Feasibility study important aspects:
*** As of Windows 10 15063 Creators Update 64-bits ***

- Provided admin rights, write at runtime testsigning entries not removable by bcdedit [v]
- Leverage arbitrary non-service key for driver-load [v]
- Use random minimal DLL with AppCertDlls key to launch driver reliably at SERVICE_SYSTEM_START time [v]
- Make auxillary loader not be easily detected by leveraging incorrectly detected AppCertDlls key [?]	(FRST64)
- Prevent display of Testmode watermark [?]
- NonpagedPoolExecute type memory allocations can still be leveraged to run work items from it [?]
- When IoCreateDriver creates a driver object based on above allocation, can a device object be created from this driver object so IoAttachDeviceToDeviceStack can be provided with this device object [?]
- Provided the name of keyboard devices are known, can the keyboard device stack reliably be understood in a way that allows to attach the device object to the e.g. KeyboardClass0 device? [?, refer to osr-online question regarding opening a handle with IoCreateFile]
  Probably it is easier to start off from keyboard kbdclass.sys driver object...
- Can the operations IoAttachDeviceToDeviceStack performs be done manually? Can with the lower and next device object pointers a fake device object be inserted into the keyboard device stack?
--> IRP_MJ_XXX array hook is almost impossible with mouse device since when moving mouse the hook is constantly being inserted and removed which greatly increases the odds for patchguard to detect that modification. Need mouse device for switching from left to right click in a first version of a driver which interfaces with the Apple touchpad.
- In safe mode: Can the driver still be loaded? Depends on whether driver itself is allowed to load and whether AppCertDlls or any other means of unauthorized code execution can be leveraged to load the driver. Does the driver *need* to be loaded in safe mode?


Question: can a driver be leveraged for giving us a handle to csrss.exe so RawInputThread may be patched?
--> For that the driver would not need to be any special, it would "just" (The capabilities of famous KProcessHacker aren't known well but as of now it does not open a handle to any protected process!) need to open a FULL ACCESS handle to csrss.exe's RawInputThread, afterwards the driver would duplicate that handle into the AppCertDlls launched process and return loading fail.
--> Provide that testsigning is activated in the first place, can csrss.exe be opened for full access without any kernel code at all? Say, is a testsigned application eligible to open a protected process? Most likely the process is not granted any special access rights however, leveraging the AppCertDlls feature might make the testsigned code gather access to csrss.exe's address space.
----------------------------
--> Provided device object is attached directly to mouclass.sys's driver object, if the entire IRP is considered, what does the mouclass.sys driver send to upper drivers when using Apple touchpad? What does it send when using a wired mouse instead? A suitable filter driver would have to transform Apple touchpad information into information Windows GUI expects.
--> Provided device object is attached directly to kbdclass.sys's driver object, if the entire IRP is considered, what does the kbdclass.sys driver send to upper drivers when using Apple keyboard? What does it send when using a wired keyboard instead? A suitable filter driver would have to transform Apple keyboard information into information Windows GUI expects.
==> Two tasks, one driver. Mostly one code routine possible, thanks to using abstractions as in professional SW-development? keyboard dispatch IS An IRP dispatch, mouse dispatch IS An IRP dispatch!